http://www.casinoaccommodations.com/privacy-policy.html

HomeCasino HotelsBy Casino1st Jackpot Casino TunicaAmeristar Casino Resort Spa Black HawkAmeristar Casino Hotel Council BluffsAmeristar Casino Hotel East ChicagoAmeristar Casino Hotel VicksburgArgosy RiversideAtlantis Paradise IslandAzamara Cruise LineBally's Las VegasBoomtown BiloxiBoomtown Casino Hotel Bossier CityBoomtown Casino Hotel New OrleansCaesars Atlantic CityCaesars Palace Las VegasCaesars Southern IndianaCelebrity Cruise LineEldorado & Silver Leagacy ResortsFlamingo Las VegasFoxwoodsHarrah's Atlantic CityHarrah's Council BluffsHarrah's Gulf CoastHarrah's JolietHarrah's Lake TahoeHarrah's Las VegasHarrah's LaughlinHarrah's Louisiana Downs CasinoHarrah's MetropolisHarrah's New OrleansHarrah's North Kansas CityHarrah's RenoHarrah's Resort Southern California Casino & ResortHarveys Lake TahoeHolland America Cruise LineHollywood Casino Gulf CoastHollywood Casino LawrenceburgHollywood Casino St. LouisHollywood Casino Sint MarteenHollywood Casino TunicaHorseshoe Bossier CityHorseshoe HammondHorseshoe TunicaL'Auberge Casino & Hotel Baton RougeThe Linq Las VegasL'Auberge Casino Resort Lake CharlesMargaritaville Resort Casino Bossier CityMohegan SunMSC Cruise LineNorwegian Cruise LineParis Las VegasPlanet HollywoodPrincess Cruise LineOceanic Cruise LineRio Las VegasRiver City Casino & HotelRoyal Beach CasinoRoyal Caribbean Cruise LineThe Cromwell Las VegasThe M Resort Spa CasinoTropicana Atlantic CityTropicana Las VegasTurning Stone Resort CasinoViejas Casino & ResortVirgin Voyages Cruise LineBy LocationAtlantic CityCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutCruisesIllinoisIndianaIowaLake TahoeLas VegasLouisianaMississippiMissouriNassau/Paradise IslandNevadaNew OrleansNew YorkThe CaribbeanRenoCruise LinesJunkets and TripsBy AirBy BusBy SeaBy LimoGroups/Special OccasionsEvents CalendarReservationsFrom the InboxMeet UsMonica JarvisEileen KasunichBuddie MackintoshPaul HahnCathy BurgessDiane JonesBeverly Godoy
CASINO ACCOMMODATIONS, LLC
General Information
This privacy policy (“Policy”) outlines the ways in which Casino Accommodations, LLC., which posts this Policy (referred to as “Casino Accommodations”, “we”, “our” or “us”) collect and use information from individuals who visit any of our Sites, social media pages or mobile applications (each a “Site” or collectively “Sites”), respond to our interactive advertisements (“Ads”), purchase goods and/or services from or engage in gaming, junket or entertainment activities offered, promoted and/or sponsored by Casino Accommodations.
What Personal Information We Collect
When you use a Site, register for an event offered, promoted and/or sponsored by, enter into a transaction with or engage in gaming activities during an event offered, promoted and/or sponsored by Casino Accommodations, you may be required to provide certain personally, identifiable information (“Personal Information”), some of which is required to be collected pursuant to federal and/or state law with respect to certain gaming transactions. Specifically, we may collect your Personal Information when you submit information to us through our Site, by email, text messages, through online forms and through other activities in which you engage on Casino Accommodation’s Site. Personal Information that we collect may include your name, address, date of birth, social security number, driver’s license number, government-issued identification card number, passport number or naturalization number, telephone number, and email address.
If you engage in gaming activity during an event offered, promoted and/or sponsored by Casino Accommodations, we may also collect certain information about your gaming activity, including your casino player club card number. (“Card Number”).
Cookies
Our Site and Ads each use cookie technology. A cookie is a small data file that is saved on your hard disk by your computer’s browser when you visit or interact with our Site or Ads. Cookies are then recognized by your Internet browser to identify you and personalize your experience and gather web statistical data, such as which pages you visit, what material you download, your Internet provider’s domain name and country, and the addresses of websites you visited immediately before, and after, visiting a particular website. The cookies we utilize do not store any Personal Information and are used to generate statistics regarding usage of our Site and to help serve relevant, targeted offers and Ads to you based on your browsing history.
Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Site.
How We Use the Information We Collect
We may use the information you provide to us for the specific purposes for which it was provided by you. We also may use the information you provide to us to: (1) communicate with you about special events, contests, sweepstakes, programs, offers, surveys and market research; (2) respond to your requests or inquiries; (3) send you promotional materials and other communications; (4) provide your personal information to our business partners; (5) at your request and consent, provide your personal information to third parties for the purpose of affording you to participate in an event that we do not offer or to a location that we do not serve;  (6) operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing, enhancing, improving and analyzing our  products, services, business and Site; managing our communications; and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions); (7) protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, claims and other liabilities; and (8) comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards, contractual obligations, and our policies.
How We Share Your Information
For business and marketing purposes, we may also disclose and share information we collect with and our business partners and any companies with which we subsequently conduct business.
When We Disclose Collected Information
Except as provided below, Casino Accommodations will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any Personal Information obtained by us without your consent. Casino Accommodations will disclose your information, including Personal Information: (1) to comply with a court order, subpoena, warrant, or other legal process; (2) to comply with legal, regulatory, or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; (3) to protect and defend Casino Accommodations, and all of its officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, and partners in connection with any legal action, claim, or dispute; (4) to enforce the terms of use of our Sites; (5) to prevent imminent physical harm; (6) to businesses that Casino Accommodations uses for purposes of performing functions on behalf of Casino Accommodations we transact business with for certain events in which you elect to participate and, including but not limited to companies that process credit card transactions; and (7) in connection with the sale, assignment, or transfer of company property or the company Sites.
Sign up for our FREE newsletters now!
Join Our Mailing List
PRIVACY POLICY
